翻译:  jamie  宛若安宁  Amber  爱撒娇的猫
我們一起購物挺開心的
It's fun that we go grocery  shopping together.
校对: 店小二
是的 我很喜歡
Yeah, I love this!
其實 你本可以待在家
You know, you could have just stayed home
看橄欖球比賽的
and watched a football game.
后期: Danica
真的嗎 Molly 真可以嗎
Could I, Molly? Could I?
噢 天吶 那好像是J.C. Small
Oh, my God, I think that's J.C. Small.
压制: 凯撒
J.C. Small是誰
Who's J.C. Small?
Janice Corb Small.
<糟糕夏日>的作者
She wrote Misbegotten Summer.
那本書影響了我的少年時期
The book defined my teenage years.
呃 我的被倍耐力年歷影響了
Huh. Mine were defined by a Pirelli Tire calendar.
以其限制級的美女寫真著稱,通常邀請最紅的超模和明星進行拍攝
等我想和一月小姐告別時 都已經六月了
It was June before I could say good-bye to Miss January.
我不確定是她不
I'm not sure if it's her.
她似乎隱居了
She's a bit of a recluse.
J.C.!
她有回頭嗎 有回頭嗎
Did she look? Did she look?
我沒看 這輪子不對勁兒
I wasn't watching. We got a hinky wheel.
它每次都往左偏 看吧
It wants to go left every time. See? Look.
噓 噓 來這邊
Shh. Shh-shh! Come here.
你說的就是她嗎
Is that who you're talking about?
別指 你在干嘛 快過來
Stop pointing! What are you doing? Come here.
好吧 我該過去跟她說話嗎
Okay, should I go in and say something to her?
如果不去 你會后悔的
You'll regret it if you don't.
芝加哥美食節時我就站在Mike Ditka旁撒尿
I peed next to Mike Ditka at Taste of Chicago.
橄欖球知名球員及教練 曾效力和執教過芝加哥熊隊
我就一直盯著他的超級碗戒指看
All I could do was stare at his Super Bowl ring.
我想我嚇著他了
I think I kind of creeped him out.
我去了 我去試一下
I'm going. I'm gonna go for it.
噢 伏特加 伏特加 是吧
Oh, vodka, vodka, vodka, huh?
好多種伏特加啊
So many choices of vodka.
噢 你喝過這個牌子的嗎
Ooh, have you ever had this brand?
我都喝過
I've had 'em all.
有最喜歡的牌子嗎
Do you have a favorite brand?
我每個都喜歡
I love 'em all equally.
我認識你
I know who you are!
- 好極了  - 耶
- Terrific.  - Yeah.
- 再見  - 嗯 再見
- See ya.  - Yeah, see ya.
等等 等等 Small女士
Wait-wait-wait-wait-wait, Ms. Small,
我想告訴您
I have to, I have to tell you
那本<糟糕夏日>改變了我人生
that Misbegotten Summer changed my life.
噢 謝謝 挺好的
Well, thank you. That's very kind.
呃 你能把手從我購物車上拿開嗎
Yeah. Could you get your hand off my cart?
噢 既然遇見你 冒昧問一句
Yeah, since I have you, can I just ask
對于躊躇滿志的作家
if you have any little piece of advice
您能給點建議嗎
for an aspiring writer?
呃 可以 要在個酗酒施暴的家庭中長大
Uh, sure. Grow up in a household of abusive alcoholics.
天啊 我媽算是個歡樂型酒鬼
God, my mom's kind of a happy drunk!
好吧 給她點時間 酒鬼起初都是快樂型的
Well, give her time. We all start off happy.
你知道嗎
You know what?
如果你真的想當作家
If you really want to be a writer,
也許你應該現在回家寫作去
maybe you should just go home and write.
- "回家寫作"  - 回家寫作
- "Go home and write."  - Go home and write.
哇 這么簡單而又深刻
Wow, it's so simple, it's profound.
- 謝謝  - 不謝
- Thank you.  - You're welcome.
你太客氣了
You're so welcome.
讓開
Move.
好的
I will.
謝謝
Thank you.
噢 我的購物車也這樣的 就這樣的
Oh, my cart does the same thing! It does!
你看見了嗎
Did you see that?
Did you see this?
免費芝士
Free cheese!
迈克和茉莉
第四季 第四集
电波诚译
就一會兒
Now this'll just take a minute.
我想看看我媽有事沒
I want to make sure my mom's okay.
好吧 她為什么會有事
Well, why-why wouldn't she be?
一個和她玩賓果游戲的朋友昨天去世了
One of her bingo friends died yesterday.
噢 真讓人難過
Aw, that's sad.
嗯 她也剛贏了個蜂蜜火腿
Yeah, she just won a HoneyBaked ham, too.
好吧 她去掉了一個贏家
Well, she went out a winner.
干嘛
What?
什么"干嘛"
What do you mean, "What""
你沒回我電話 我擔心你呢
You don't return my calls. I'm worried about you.
沒什么好擔心的
Nothing to be worried about.
進來吧 有火腿
Come on in. I got ham.
我愛火腿
I do love bingo ham.
屋里怎么這么暗
Why is it so dark in here?
我在演練身后事
I'm practicing for when I'm dead.
媽 別這樣嘛
Ma, don't be that way.
沒人能活著離開的 Mikey
Nobody gets out of here alive, Mikey!
她還好啊
She's fine.
來吧 趁著沒腐爛快吃吧
Here. Eat it before it rots.
每個人都有那么一天
A fate that awaits us all.
正解 正解
So true, so true.
有芥末嗎
You got mustard?
Carl!
媽 你不能就此消沉啊
Ma, you can't give in to this depression.
- 我知道你思念朋友  - 朋友
- I know you miss your friend.  - Friend?
我受夠那個不敬神明的臭婊子了
I couldn't stand that godless whore.
哦 既然你那么討厭她 那你還難過什么
Well, if you hated her so much, why are you upset?
12年來坐她旁邊玩游戲
Sat next to her at bingo for 12 years.
我們從來都是惡語相向
Never had a kind word to say to each other.
昨晚 她在彌留之際 拉著我的手
Last night, right before she died, she took my hand,
看著我的眼睛說 "下一個就是你了"
looked into my eyes and said, "You're next."
呃 我想她沒什么惡意
Well, I'm sure she didn't mean anything by it.
當真
Really?
在我看來 很明顯啊
Sounded kind of specific to me.
Carl!
周日過來吃晚飯吧
Why don't you come over for dinner on Sunday?
你會開心的
It'll cheer you up.
呃 那群人很討厭
Uch! Those people are awful.
幾點
What time?
這是求救信號吧
Well, there's a cry for help.
等一下 Calvin
Hang on, Calvin!
我還有瓶子給你
I got some other bottles for you!
噢 你不是那個流浪漢
Oh, you're not my homeless guy.
不是的
No, I'm not.
我叫Molly
I'm Molly from yesterday.
在超市你叫我走開 別煩你
in supermarket you told me to go away and leave you alone.
你怎么發現我住這的
How the hell did you find out where I live?
呃 我可能尾隨你到家門口
Well, I may have followed you home,
不過不是跟蹤狂那種跟蹤
but not in a stalkery way.
是"我是你的腦殘粉"這種跟蹤
Like a kind of "I'm your biggest fan!" Kind of way.
雖然是有點跟蹤狂
Which is a little stalkery,
我 不會再說這詞了
but I'm just gonna, I'm gonna stop saying stalkery.
等等 別這樣
So wait, wait! Come on!
我按你的意見 寫了整整一夜
I took your advice. I stayed up all night writing,
我只想讓你看看 告訴我
and I just want you to take a look at it and tell me
我是不是在浪費時間
if I'm wasting my time!
你是在浪費時間
You're wasting your time.
哦 天啊
Oh! Ow! God!
把腳挪開
Get your foot out!
你毀了我的系統
You ruined my system.
雖然我想問的很多
Come on. I know it's a lot to ask,
但我只是想說一件事
but I-I just want to be able to say one thing
向你證明 我是真的想當作家
to try to convince you that I really want to be a writer.
就一件
One thing.
就是這個
That's the thing.
這真的有必要嗎
Is this really necessary?
在看到你媽媽那可憐的狀態后
After I saw the pitiful state your mom was in,
我有點擔心了
I got worried.
奶奶
Grandma!
這音樂太吵了
That music's awful loud.
她要是摔倒了或者突發心臟病的話
I mean, if she fell or had a heart attack,
沒人能聽見她求救啊
nobody could hear her yell for help.
別激動
Take it easy.
還是你別激動吧
You take it easy.
我們上次說話就是在吵架
Last time we talked, it was a fight.
你上次跟誰說話 都是在吵架啊
Last time you talked to anybody, it was a fight!
奶奶
Grandma!
請問你有事嗎
Can I help you?
怎么回事
What is going on?
我在這兒像個瘋子一樣敲門
I'm out here knocking like a crazy person.
抱歉 我們看到警車了
Sorry, we saw the police car.
不知道是你啊
We didn't know it was you.
“我們”指誰啊
"We" Who?
姐妹教堂的一些教友
Some members of our sister church
從烏干達來訪問
are visiting from Uganda.
這幫非洲人居然會開派對
And damn if those Africans don't know how to party.
派對 現在才上午11點啊
Party? It's 11:00 a.M.
在非洲可不是
Not in Africa.
走吧 Carl
Let's go, Carl.
再見 奶奶 好好開派對吧
Bye, Nana. Enjoy your party.
好的
Okay.
呃 好尷尬啊
Oh... this is awkward.
samuel 你在這兒干什么呢
Samuel, what the hell are you doing here?
孩子 快進來
Come on in, child.
這兒有好多善良的非洲基督教女孩兒
I got a lot of good Christian African girls
等著見你呢
waiting to meet you.
我愛死你奶奶了
I love your grandmother.
怎么你邀請他來派對
How are you gonna invite him to the party
都不邀請你的親孫子呢
but not your own grandson?
我更喜歡他啊
I like him better.
哈
Huh.
這是"哼" 還是"哈"
Is that-Is that like a Hmm? Or like a Huh!
我還是 閉嘴吧
I'm gonna, I'm gonna just stop.
你 好好讀吧
You... I'm gonna let you read.
- 看完了  - 然后呢
- I'm done.  - And?
愛死了
Loved it.
- 不會吧  - 沒錯
- No! - Oh, yeah.
你的語言混合了
Your use of language is a cross between
Virginia Woolf和Dean Koontz早期的風格
Virginia Woolf and early Dean Koontz.
Virginia Woolf 英國女性主義作家     Dean Koontz  美國著名懸疑小說作家
我就知道 天啊  我現在該怎么做
I knew it. Oh, my God, what do I do now?
用找個經紀人嗎 哦 我應該找個出版商
I mean, do I get an agent? Oh, I gotta get a publisher.
不 你什么都不用干
No, you don't have to do anything.
如此佳作 他們會來找你的
With writing that good, they're gonna find you.
哦 天啊 實在太棒了
Oh, my God! That's awesome!
- 是啊  - 我的天啊
- Yeah.  - Oh, my God.
在致謝頁里 好好謝謝我
I want a big, big thank you on that dedication page...
- 好的  - 好嗎
- Okay. ...  - all right?
- 好的  - 那就這樣
- Okay.  - All right.
好的 再見了
All right. Bye.
你不是 為了趕我走
You're not, you're not just saying it's good
才這么說的吧
to get rid of me?
怎么會呢
No...
嘿 我是不會走的
Hey, I am not leaving
除非你告訴我你真實的看法
until you give me your honest opinion.
你不會想聽的
You don't want it.
我為了當作家放棄了一切
I gave up everything to be a writer.
噢
Oof.
不可能那么糟糕吧
Okay, it can't be that bad.
你讀過嗎
Did you read it?
我當然讀了 我寫的啊
Of course I read it. I wrote it.
問題就在這 這是你寫的 不是你經歷的
Well, that's the problem, you wrote it. You didn't live it.
那里面沒一樣是真的 沒有
There's nothing real in those pages. Nothing.
開玩笑呢吧
Are you kidding?!
還有什么能比一個旁遮普少年
What could be more real than a young Punjabi boy
在孟買貧民窟奮斗的故事更真實的呢
struggling in the slums of Mumbai?!
這是我讀過的最差的開頭
The opening paragraph was the worst writing I've ever read.
如果讓我挖出雙眼塞進菊花
If I could gouge out my eyeballs and stuff them up my ass
就可以不再看這些東西的話
so I never had to read those words again,
我會這么做的
I would do so.
你是說 刪掉第一
So are you, are you saying cut the first,
刪掉第一段
cut the first paragraph?
我是說
I am saying...
天啊  真要把我逼瘋了
Oh, God, it drives me crazy,
有些人總覺得自己拿著豪華筆記本
people that think they're writers just 'cause
坐在星巴克 他們就是作家了
they have a fancy laptop and a cushy seat in Starbucks.
嗨 我告訴你
Hey, for your information,
我的筆記本還是windows95系統
my laptop is running Windows '95.
我的文章是在我媽的餐桌上寫的
And I wrote this at my mom's kitchen table
因為我還跟她住在一起
because I still live with her.
你多大了啊
How old are you?
30出頭 30多歲 不到40吧
Like, early, middle-late, late-early 30s.
你還和你媽住在一起
And you are still living with your mother?
不是奇葩的那種
Not in a weird way.
我和我丈夫 她丈夫 還有我妹妹
I'm with my husband and her husband and my sister.
天啊 別想什么孟買了
Well, for God's sake, forget about Mumbai!
寫寫你自己的悲慘生活吧
Write about your own pathetic life.
對啊  天啊 你太棒了
Right! God, you're good!
我悲慘的事兒可多著呢
I mean, I got tons of pathetic!
你得深入挖掘
You've gotta dig deep. You know,
人們都說你應該寫
people say that you should write about
你知道的事 那是胡說
what you know, but that's bull.
你應該寫你不想讓人知道的事
You want to write what you don't want people to know.
好 等一下 等下
Okay, hang on, hang on.
- "不想" - 不想讓人知道
- "Don't want..." - Want people to know.
噢 讓人知道
Ooh, ooh! People to know.
"讓人知道"
"...people to know."
就是這樣
That's right.
我不想再見到你
So I don't want to see your face again
除非你給我帶來的作品 夠深刻 夠優秀
till you bring me something deep, something good,
夠真實 還有更大瓶的伏特加
something real, and a bigger bottle of vodka.
好的 不見面 要更大瓶
Okay, so no, no face, bigger bottle.
- 好的  - 好的
- Okay.  - All right.
- 寫 寫 - 對 對
- Write. Write. - Right. Oh, right.
- 寫  - 好的
- Write.  - Okay.
等下 等下
Oh, wait-wait-wait.
呃 其實 真是抱歉
Um, actually, sorry.
我也不知道這個怎么進來的
I don't know how this got in there,
但是這
but it's...
我想你不會讓我
I didn't think you were gonna let me...
- 出去吧  - 好的
- Get out!  - Okay.
實在太棒了 她完全拆解了我
It was amazing. She completely dismantled me.
拆了個七零八落
Just tore me down.
下一分鐘 又把我重新裝好
And the next minute, built me right back up.
他們重塑一個海軍陸戰隊員需要六個月呢
You know, it takes them six months to do that to a Marine.
她只用一瓶伏特加就搞定了
She did it to me in one bottle of vodka.
那么她喜歡你的故事嘍
So she likes your story?
不 她發自內心地討厭它
No, hated it with every fiber of her being.
那我就糊涂了 你開心什么
Okay, I'm confused. Why are you happy?
因為她告訴我
Because she told me exactly
如何更好地寫作
what I have to do to become a better writer.
要深入挖掘
I have to dig deeper.
挖哪
Where?
這兒 這兒
Here and here.
還有這里所有地方
And all up in here.
你想過為什么我們到現在還和我媽住一起嗎
Did you ever wonder why we still live with my mother?
日日憂思
Every day.
我過去覺得 是因為我們沒能力
I mean, I used to think it was because we couldn't
另立門戶
afford a place of our own.
確實如此
Well, we can't.
你辭職了 我們欠了很多信用卡債
You quit your job and we have a ton of credit card debt.
我是說情感上
I'm talking emotionally.
數字是小事
Numbers mean nothing.
都刷爆六張卡了
It's six maxed-out cards.
欠了8萬 可不是小事
That's about 80 grand away from nothing.
呃 我
Well, I...
我得思索些嚴肅的問題了
I need to start asking the hard questions.
為什么我還在靠賒賬過日子
I mean, why am I still in O.A.?
為什么Victoria是個癮君子
Why is Victoria a pothead?
怪叔叔Frankie身上究竟發生了什么
And whatever really happened to weird Uncle Frankie?
你有個怪叔叔叫Frankie 我也有個怪叔叔叫Frankie誒
You had a weird Uncle Frankie? I had a weird Uncle Frankie.
我們家那個是斜眼兒
Yeah, mine had a wonky eye
開一輛破舊的凱迪拉克
and drove this beat-up old Cadillac.
我叔叔也是
So did mine.
- 好了 今晚不聊了  - 好的
- Okay, that's enough questions for tonight. - Yeah.
我喜歡這個尊巴舞
I love this Zumba.
不像是在鍛煉
Doesn't feel like a workout.
更像在俱樂部里熱舞
It's more like we're dancing at a club.
就差一個想送我回家的
All that's missing is a coked-up Persian
磕了藥的波斯人
trying to give me a ride home.
嗨 親愛的
Hey, sweetie.
想跳你的梅倫格舞嗎
Care to get your Merengue on?
算了 我現在腦子有點亂
Um, not really, I got a lot on my mind right now.
想談談嗎
Want to talk about it?
好的 我確實想
Yeah, actually, I do.
估計會很有幫助
Think that could be really helpful.
好吧 呃
Okay, uh...
我最近一直在回憶童年
I've been, I've been thinking a lot about my childhood lately.
回憶那個干嘛
What the hell you doing that for?
因為當你的導師告訴你"深入挖掘"時
Because when your mentor tells you to "Dig deep,"
你就要去深挖
by God, you dig deep.
然后 深挖
And... dig deep.
嗯 大部分時間你都很開心
Well, for the most part you were a happy kid.
是嗎 真的
Yeah? Really?
幾乎開心過了頭
Well, almost too happy.
有一段時間
For a while there we thought
我們覺得你是個傻孩子
you were one of those slow kid
你老是傻笑 亂抱陌生人
Always smiling, hugging strangers.
你在后院吃土 一坐就是幾個小時
You'd sit in the backyard for hours just eating dirt.
你居然讓我吃土
You let me, you let me eat dirt?
那種 很臟的土嗎
Like, like dirt dirt?
你的身體知道你的需求
The body knows what it needs.
我就是覺得很對不起那條狗
The thing I feel really bad about is the dog.
- Monroe  - 是啊
- Monroe? - Yeah.
我們拋棄了他 因為我們以為
We got rid of him 'cause we thought
后院那些洞都是他挖的
he was the one making all the holes in the yard.
你告訴我他被車撞死了
You told me he got hit by a car.
如果我說他被送到一個農場去了
Well, if I said he was living on a farm,
你就會想去看他
you'd want to go visit him.
那埋在盒子里的是誰
Well, then, who did we bury in the box?
那個一直要媽媽的破娃娃
That horrible doll that wouldn't quit asking for its mama.
你殺了睡眠寶寶
You killed Sleepy Time Baby Girl?
嗨 媽 你今天感覺好點了嗎
Hey, Ma. You feeling better today?
我在烤箱里放了土豆 而不是我腦袋
I put the potatoes in the oven and not my head.
所以 還不錯吧
So there's that.
還有這種
There's that great
建立在自殺上的幽默感
suicide-based sense of humor.
我去加熱
I'll go heat these up.
嘿
Hey!
Biggs老媽
Mother Biggs.
怎么了
What's going on?
我朋友去世了
My friend died.
你居然有朋友
You had a friend?
請節哀
My condolences.
最近天氣挺冷哈
Bit of a cold snap we're having, huh?
你不用在這沒話找話
Don't feel you need to make conversation on my account.
太好了 我也有點詞窮了
Good, 'cause that kind of tapped me out.
我挖得越深就越覺得
The more I dig, the clearer it becomes.
我媽毀了我的童年
My mother ruined my childhood.
你在說什么呢
What are you talking about?
你這不挺好的嗎
You turned out fine.
是嗎 Mike
Yeah, did I, Mike?
真的嗎
Did I?
我想說是 但你問了兩次
I was gonna say yes, but you asked twice.
我現在要重新想想
So now I'm rethinking my answer.
- 我以為你想挖些隱情  - 確實
- I thought you wanted to dig up some dirt. - I did.
只是沒想到 我自食惡果了
But I didn't think I'd be the one eating it.
誰知道她還騙了我多少事啊
I mean, who knows what else she's been lying about?
自從我來了大姨媽
I mean, she told me I had to quit tap-dancing
她讓我別跳踢踏舞了
after I got my period because she said
因為她說那會傷害卵巢
it would scramble my ovaries.
真的嗎
Is that true?
我不知道
I don't know!
我什么也不知道了
I don't know anything anymore.
我不知道 我是否真的對蘑菇過敏
I mean, I don't know, am I even really allergic to mushrooms?
可能沒事 看
I... Probably not, here.
呃 我
Well, I...
完全沒事
No, nothing.
不 有事
No, I'm getting it.
你是吃苯海拉明還是什么
Do you need a Benadryl or something?
在這 在這 來 來 來
Here, here, here, here, here, here.
咽下去 咽下去
Down, down, down, down.
好啦 好啦
Oh, oh, okay, okay, okay!
好了 各位
Okay, everybody.
開動吧
Let's eat.
親愛的主
Dear Lord.
感謝您的慷慨恩賜
We thank you for this wonderful bounty.
愿您今夜心懷慈悲
Tonight I ask that you hold me in your grace
不因同伴之失責罰于我
and not judge me because of the company I keep.
阿門
Amen.
能把羊角面包遞給我嗎
Can you pass the rolls?
當然 能告訴我生父是誰嗎
Yeah, sure, can you tell me who my real father was?
你在說什么啊
What are you talking about?
看看我們倆
Look at us, okay?
倆閨女長得并不像
One of these things is not like the other.
我倆誰是雜種 媽
So, who's the mutt, Mom?
她爹是在收留Monroe的那個農場嗎
Is her father on the farm with Monroe?
還是怪叔叔Frankie是她爹
Or weird Uncle Frankie?
我弟弟Frankie嗎
My brother Frankie?
不是一個Frankie 媽 別再追究了
Different Frankie, Ma. Let it go.
媽 她在說啥
m, what's she talking about?
我不知道
I have no idea.
我對你爸一直忠貞不渝
I was faithful to your father.
我是在你爸入土為安之后
That sweet angel was cold in the ground
才上馬復出的
before I got back on that horse.
我看 是被馬上了吧
Yeah, or under it.
我那時還年輕
Hey! I was still a young woman.
我能怎樣 把下面塞住嗎
What was I supposed to do, put a cork in it?
我在蒂華納看過一次
I saw that once in Tijuana.
把青豆遞給我
Pass the green beans.
那我的飯量問題呢
And what about my issues with food?
居住現狀問題呢
Or the-the fact that I still live here?
選男人沒眼光的問題呢
Or my poor choices in men?
- 喂  - 不是指你
- Hey! - Not you.
在你之前的一排基佬
The chorus line of gay guys before you.
嗯 那就好
Okay, that's fair.
歸根結底都是因為這個紅頭發女人
Okay, it all traces back to one little redhead.
和我不像 和她也不像
Who I don't look like, and neither does she.
你是我媽嗎
Are you my mother?!
哦 閉嘴吃飯
Oh, shut up!
不要 我們偏不
No, we're not gonna shut up!
我們已經沉默太久了
We've been silent too long!
你只有吃土的時候
The only time you've been silent
才能安靜
is when you had dirt in your mouth.
不然我怎么會放任你啃了半個院子呢
Why'd you think I let you eat half the backyard?
因為你喝醉了
Because you were drunk!
因為你太討厭
'Cause you were a pain in the ass!
你想過為什么嗎
Yeah, did you ever ask why?
想知道原因嗎
You want to know why?!
去死吧 這就是原因
Screw you, that's why!
你拿面包扔我
You threw a roll at me?
因為我夠不著土豆泥
Couldn't reach the potatoes!
是嗎 我來幫你啊
Yeah? Well, let me help you!
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey!
我還一口沒吃呢
I haven't had any yet.
啊
Aah!
干嘛打我
What did I do?
你娶了她
You married her and you won't
卻還讓她賴在我這
get her out of the house!
那是因為她金錢意識差
It's 'cause she's horrible with money!
嘿
Hey!
你別攪和進來
You stay out of this!
那我呢
Well, what about me?!
我也是這家的一份子
I'm part of this family, too!
- 不是嗎  - 閉嘴吧你
- Aren't I?! - Shut up!
天
Oh, my...
不管了 活命要緊
Damn it, I choose life!
救命
Help!
天啊 太糟了 一家子都恨我了
God, it was awful. My whole family hates me.
嗯
Mm.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
這是成為真正作家的第一步
That's the first step in becoming a real writer.
我已經有四本書的時間沒和家人聯系了
I haven't talked to my family in four books.
那可太悲催了
Oh, God, that's so sad. Mm.
不會呀 我更愿意被千千萬萬的讀者愛著
No, it's much better to be loved by millions of readers
而不是被六個從同一"前庭"跌落的人喜愛
than six people who happened to fall out of the same vagina.
大家庭呀
Big family.
是"大前庭"才對
Big vagina.
我只是
Yeah, I just, you know,
the thing is I...
我還是很愛家人的
I kind of love my family.
你不是想當作家嗎
I thought you wanted to be a writer?
我想呀
Oh, I do.
那這才是你的新家人
Well, then this is your new family.
雖然可能沒什么人味
It may not have much personality,
但起碼不會在你胸部發育時 對你動手動腳
but it won't molest you when you get your boobies.
我滴個神啊
Oh, God!
真抱歉
Sorry.
沒什么
That's all right, I mean,
誰都有個怪叔叔 對吧
everybody's got a weird uncle, right?
我不知道 但我真的
I don't know, I'm just not really that comfortable
不太喜歡曬家丑
airing my family's dirty laundry.
這樣吧
Aw, you know what?
我們不談這個了
We don't have to talk about it anymore.
你今天也夠受的了
I mean, you've had a pretty rough day.
你應該放松一下
Yeah. You should just relax.
你頭發上還有土豆泥呢
You got potato in your hair still.
咳 我知道
Oh, I know.
我的天
Oh, my God.
快看
Look at that.
看看這可愛的小臉
Look at that sweet face. Oh, my.
就這樣
There it is.
- 還有小酒窩 - 是 是
- Little dimples there! - Aw! Yup, yup.
瞧瞧
Look at that...
謝謝啦
Yes, thank you.
- 謝謝啦  - 嗯 好的
- Thank you. - Yeah. Oh, yeah.
如果你想清理干凈的話
Well, you know, if you wanted to clean up,
咱們可以來個雙人浴
we could take a bath.
問題是
You know, the thing is
我真的
I'm-I'm really,
只在家里洗澡
uh, kind of a home showerer.
*饑渴的眼神*
*Hungry eyes*
<Hungry eyes> by Eric Carmen
*我們是不期而遇嗎*
*Did I take you by surprise... ?*
Flynn 我覺得
You know, Flynn, I think
你確實有潛力
that you have real potential.
我覺得你有那種
I'm feeling like you've got those...
饑渴的眼神
hungry eyes, yeah.
嗯
Oh...
那個 已經
You know, it's getting pr...
已經很晚了 我不想
...pretty late and I don't want to...
- 不想打擾你休息了 - 別說話
I don't want to put you out or anything... Just don't talk.
- 我  - 別說話
- I... - Do not talk.
天 我
Oh, gosh, am I...
是不是占了你的椅子
am I in your chair?
等等
Let me...
行了 這
There we go, that's...
這下好多了
that's better.
現在我知道了
Now, I know
你為什么那天跟蹤我回家了
why you followed me home the other day.
嗯 我該
Oh, God, I should...
回去找我的警察老公了
I should be getting back to my police officer husband
他知道我在這呢
who knows exactly where I am.
不 你待在這兒別動
No, I think you should just stay right here.
我去樓上拿兩件和服來
And I'm gonna run up and get us a couple of kimonos.
好吧
Okay.
哦
Oh!
這樣就不緊張了吧
I like to get that out of the way.
不行了
Nope.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组